bandlab.com 2013-09-28

# JamHub - Privacy Policy

We at JamHub Corporation respect your concerns about privacy and value the relationship we have with you. This Privacy Notice describes the types of personal information we collect on www.jamhub.com, how we may use that information, and with whom we may share it.

Except as otherwise provided herein, any communication or material you post or transmit to JamHub electronically is, and will be treated as, non-confidential and non-proprietary. By transmitting or posting any communication or material to this website or via electronic mail, you agree that JamHub or any of its affiliates may use your communication as material for any purpose, including, but not limited to reproduction, transmission, publication, broadcast, and posting. Furthermore, you hereby agree not to transmit any unlawful, threatening, libelous, defamatory, obscene, pornographic, or profane material or any material that could constitute or encourage conduct that would be considered a criminal offense, give rise to civil liability, or violate any law.

Your Internet Protocol (IP) address and other website usage data may be collected and used to gather broad demographic information. JamHub may set and access JamHub cookies on your computer to, among other things, customize the user experience. We use user IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the website, and track user movement for aggregate use. Monitoring such user behavior enables us to provide our users with an ever-improving website, service, and general offering. We do not link IP addresses to personally identifiable information. You may realize certain losses of functionality if you turn your cookies off in your browser.

Affiliates, vendors, advertisers, and other non-related third parties displayed on JamHub may also contain cookies or tag your computer with cookies. JamHub does not control these third party cookies and, for your own benefit, you should check the privacy policy of such third parties. Third party ads displayed on JamHub may also include tags enabling such third parties to collect information about the user's interaction with such ads.

You are not required to provide personal information to use many aspects of this website. If we do obtain your personal information, we will keep all such information confidential and we will not sell, rent, trade or otherwise disclose it, except as described here. We may share the information you provide with companies that are affiliated or contracting with JamHub, provided such affiliates or contracting parties comply with applicable legal requirements in protecting your personal information. We also share information provided by our website visitors with strategic partners or service providers we have retained to perform services on our behalf. In addition, we may share information about you with distributors, dealers or resellers of the items you purchase through this website. We may also disclose information about you (i) if we are required to do so by law or legal process, (ii) to law enforcement authorities or other government officials, or (iii) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity.

We reserve the right to transfer any information we have about you in the event of a disposition of all or a portion of our business and/or assets. Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to try to ensure that the transferee uses personal information you have provided through this website in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice and applicable laws.

### Jurisdiction

Any legal issues arising in connection with this website shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the Commonwealth of Massachusetts, without giving effect to any principles of conflicts of law of that or any other jurisdiction.

Those who access the website from locations outside the United States do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with local laws if and to the extent local laws are applicable. This website is not intended to subject JamHub to the laws or jurisdiction of any state, country or territory other than the Commonwealth of Massachusetts.

### Miscellaneous

If any provision of these Terms of Use is unlawful, void or unenforceable, the remaining provisions of the Terms of Use shall remain in place. These Terms of Use constitute the entire agreement and understanding between you and JamHub with respect to use of the website, superseding all prior or contemporaneous communications. A printed version of these Terms of Use shall be admissible in judicial or administrative proceedings based on or relating to use of the website to the same extent and subject to the same conditions as other business documents and records originally generated and maintained in printed form.

### How to Contact Us

If you have any questions about our information practices, please contact us by:

Email: info@JamHub.com  
Calling: (877) 526-4827 [(877) JAM-HUBS] (USA)  
Writing: JamHub Corporation  
PO BOX 482  
Whitinsville, MA 01588  
Copyright Notice

All pages of the JamHub website are Copyright © 2009-2013 JamHub Corporation. All Rights Reserved
